hackersonlineclub.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy - HackersOnlineClub

**If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy,  please feel free to contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**

At hackersonlineclub.com the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by hackersonlineclub.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, hackersonlineclub.com makes use of log files.

The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site.

These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising.

**Hackersonlineclub.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.**
